ANCHOR ADAMS

Snohomish, WA · 435-345-7083 anchor.adams@znws.com

Z Networks Marysville, WA

TO ADMINISTRATIVE TEAM,

Prior to joining Z Networks as an IT Technician, I was a graduate of Everett Community College and was the FIRST EVER STUDENT IN THE IT DEPARTMENT TO GRADUATE WITH HONORS AND A 4.0 GPA. Less than a week after graduating, I accepted an offer with F1 Consultancy as a Technical Consultant where I immediately joined the Wireless network team and quickly became a Network Consultant. Due to my success, dedication, and proven leadership abilities, I was scheduled as the network lead for a March 2020 event. I am a great candidate for the **Helpdesk Coordinator Job** because of my ability and willingness to communicate, leadership traits, proven attention to process, and willingness to follow process even when under scrutiny.

As an IT Technician with Z Networks, I have gained an understanding of the expectations for the company and its clients. I have proven to be willing to follow the process and find answers when there are different perspectives on processes in place. With a track record of reliability and positivity, I work well with others and get the job done! I look forward to this growth opportunity within Z Networks.

Along with the formal education at Everett Community College, my extensive experience in the food industry, manufacturing, construction, and IT roles have allowed me to hone many crucial skills over the years:

- Excel in customer service.
- Work well with other team members, in both leadership and entry level roles.
- Willing and capable of traveling and working long hours.
- Cisco Certified Network Associate.
- Experienced WiFi channel planning and Xirrus arrays.
- A+ Certified.
- Experienced in IT and Network troubleshooting and monitoring using Fluke devices and Solarwinds monitoring software.
- Helpdesk experienced

I am hungry to learn, strive for excellence, embrace process, and look forward to making the contributions this position will offer to our team.

Thank you for your time and consideration,

Anchor Adams



ANCHOR ADAMS

AnchorAdams86@gmail.com 425-345-7083 Snohomish, WA



CERTIFICATIONS

- CCNA, Cisco ID: CSCO13412597
- CompTIA A+
- MTA: Windows Server Administration Fundamentals
- LPI 010-160: Linux Essentials

- MTA: Networking Fundamentals
- MTA: Mobility and Device Fundamentals
- MTA: Security Fundamentals
- CLO-001: CompTIA Cloud Essentials

SKILLS

- Customer assistance
- Troubleshooting
- Network Deployment
- Linux
- Xirrus WiFi Arrays
- Fluke Network testing devices
- Helpdesk

- Management
- Extensive safety training
- Microsoft Windows
- Network Configuration
- Cisco
- Meraki
- Ticketing Software

- Blueprint interpretation
- Office and Logistic software
- Active Directory
- Cloud Configuration
- WiFi Channel Planning
- WDS
- Quickly learn & troubleshoot software

EDUCATION

APRIL 2018 – AUGUST 2019
STUDENT, EVERETT COMMUNITY COLLEGE

GRADUATED WITH HONORS & 4.0 GPA while earning the following:

- Information Technology –ATA Degree
- Computer Support Specialist Certificate
- Cybersecurity Analyst Certificate

- Systems Administrator Certificate
- Network Administrator Certificate

ACTIVITIES AND AWARDS

- The first student to graduate with honors and a 4.0 GPA from the IT program at Everett Community College.
- Volunteered as a member of a team to conduct a "pentest" for an organization. We were able to expose network vulnerabilities to be addressed immediately.
- Vice president of Ethical Hacking Club
- Academic excellence, 4.0 GPA at EvCC
- Create a single domain across AWS and GCP with three domain controllers properly replicating between the two cloud environments.

EXPERIENCE

FEBURARY 2021 - PRESENT

IT TECHNITIAN Z NETWORKS

Z Networks provides IT support for small to medium sized companies. The level of support is based on the client needs. This ranges from a one-time consultancy to designing, deploying, and maintaining a full IT infrastructure along with providing helpdesk, security, and on-site support. Some requirements of this position are:

- Communicate with co-workers, team lead, and coordination department to ensure the best service for all clients.
- Work effectively both in a team environment and on individual tasks.
- Maintain courteous and professional interaction with co-works via phone, email, instant messaging and in person.
- Effectively communicate with other vendors and ISPs on behalf of Z Networks clients to address issues and projects.
- Follow process to ensure all IT Technicians are consistently providing the same excellent service.
- Collaborate with administrative team to update processes for a more efficient workflow.
- Utilize a proprietary ticketing system to support client issues quickly and effectively as they arise.
- Troubleshoot network connectivity issues.
- Troubleshoot hardware and software issues.
- Perform maintenance and basic system administrative tasks on Windows server 2008 and up.
- Support many different businesses and environments.

FEBURARY 2019 – MARCH 2020

TECHNICAL CONSULTANT/ NETWORK CONSULTANT F1 CONSULTANCY LTD / LLC

F1 Consultancy provides IT and network support to events around the world of all sizes. Some requirements of this position were:

- Communicate with the client to ensure our deployment and support exceeds their expectations.
- Work effectively both in a team environment and on individual tasks.
- Maintain courteous and professional interaction with the attendees and event staff (this often came when someone would unplug a network device).
- Deploy network backbone, bulk cat5e cable, routers, switches, and arrays to designated locations as specified by blueprints.
- Troubleshoot network connectivity issues using Fluke testing tools.
- Develop and utilize WDS (Server 2012 R2) to configure up to 5000 MS WINDOWS devices for upcoming events.
- Channel plan, configure and deploy Xirrus wireless arrays.
- Assist warehouse employees with asset management.
- Preform quality tests and configure hardware; including Xbox, Microsoft Surface, laptops, Cisco networking equipment, and Xirrus arrays; using licensed and proprietary software.
- Monitor network devices and test wireless availability for the event.

OCTOBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2017

CONCRETE FOUNDATION LABORER, POWERS CONCRETE INC

- Utilize math skills for precise measurements.
- Effectively communicate with supervisor and team members.
- Follow guidelines and instruction of supervisor.

JUNE 2016 - OCTOBER 2016

TOW TRUCK OPERATOR, R & R STAR

- Ability to work long shifts, including on call.
- Tend to the needs of customers in a timely manner with a friendly and helpful attitude.